Yes, friends, here the
numbers for the quarter for ICICI Lombard have come,
so we will talk about that in this video,
but I will
tell you its LIC on a year-on-year basis, I will
tell you the quarter-on-quarter comparison, and
I am also going to
tell you the comparison of the financial year on a year-on-year basis, so let's
start, so first of all,
if we talk about quarter-on-quarter,
we have seen a grade of 22.4 in its income,
now in the total income, that is, the revenue of the company,
we have seen a change of 22.4 in the revenue,
if we
compare it with the January-March quarter of last year, and the
total income of the company here in this total quarter is Rs.
crore, and see, this has given good growth, and if
we compare it with the previous quarter, which is the
October-December quarter of 2020,
then we have seen a
growth of 40 percent in the total income, so it is
seen that this quarter  The
company has commented well last year itself
and has commented better than the previous quarter as well.
Now let's talk about the ATM Nagaram
financial year, which
is the entire financial year from April to
March. If we compare it with the previous April to
March financial year of 1920, if we compare it with the previous April to March financial year, then
we have seen a growth of 0.1 percent in revenue there
and the
total income of the company in this entire year was 12th Ujjain
160 1.37 crores. See, if
we are seeing the company's net revenue during the quarter, then it is a
simple thing that the company is performing well. So let us
tell you that
from April to June the company's revenue was almost
negligible, so because of that
you are seeing this much growth here,
but if there is
no negative growth here even during the quarter, then it is a simple thing that it is
performing very well.
Now here we talk about
profitability. So first of all, let us look at the
last quarter cycle profit.  If we
compare it with the previous quarter, we have
seen a 10% growth in profitability here. Now,
look at the previous quarter, which is the October
to December quarter, Twenty20, that is,
water three. If we
compare that, then we have seen a grade of 10%
in profitability here.
And after this, if
I compare it with the last year's January to March quarter, then
we can see a grade of change at 222
in profitability here as well
because we have seen a very good growth here.
Now, if we talk about the Red and
White financial year, that is, if we
talk about the period from April to March, then in that
too, we have seen a growth of 23% change as compared to the
financial year of 1920.
Because if we look at the time of wind,
if we are seeing a growth of change at 323
in profitability,
I think the consultant was
ICICI Lombard here, he seems to be commenting on good.
And there is
good news for its shareholders, here ICICI
Lombard has declared dividend on the previous fee of the share,
if you have
10 clear then you will get a dividend of ₹50, so
see and if I look at it, if we
leave aside the liquid situation, if
we leave aside the results of the entire financial year,
here the results of the company
seem really good to me and I would
like it or not because we have seen that from
January to March, Sushil Jat, you
saw Tata Motors,
whatever seal data of the automobile industry, when we have seen it, we have
seen good growth, so you all know
that all the automobiles, that is, all the
cars, etc., trucks, etc., all of them are
insured, if seen then it is a simple
thing, this message channel goes into insurance, other
insurances also go for their horse insurance,
their insurance help
venture into Gaya, house insurance, there are very
good different insurances, by the way, mobile
internet such insurances come, but the main
insurance, which is the main insurance of these, which is the revenue
contribution of these, gives
cars, Michael, fruits, Michael  Their
main business is through inter-chain trading. I think a
very good growth is
visible here in ICICI Lombard. I would
say for its shares, its market price is
many times higher than the market price. ICICI Lombard has given good results here.
If you look here, its running rate is
25.71 and which has now become
57. So, see, this is
a very good thing here. But this is the
animal ratio. Last year, using these purchases of
31, there has been a warning here. The
line of face seven, this
very good tightening visibility is also visible
and the company is also showing good comments here.
Look, if we talk about that person here, then
its book value is 20.51, so at which, at 11:00,
this general insurance company of Arora Khatri is
trending at such a valuation. You should know
that ICICI Lombard is a private company.
Meanwhile, you will see
radio activity only on premium valuations. If you
see, you are
definitely getting a little expensive jewellery on the channel as compared to the industry,
but see, this company is very good.
Now the way it is showing growth,
you will always see it trailing at premium valuations.
Now see,
we have been seeing continuous revenue growth for the last 4 years
and after that, if you
look at the ATM graph profitability,
we have seen the profitability also increasing every year.
Last year on 11th, there was a profit of Rs 90 crore,
which has now become Rs 1473
crore, a profit of about Rs 300 crore.
Here, this time we have seen an increase. If you
look at it, the company is performing very well.
Otherwise, it has been revenue
content once, but see, the revenue is one and a half
inch more. So, we know that during Corbett's
time, there was more insurance sales, so
due to that, revenue
content is visible here. So, if you
look here, the share of ICICI Lombard is
trending at 30.  And if you only
see its 1628, you are getting
it right now on almost ₹10 correction with your own hands friends, that
means
correction of 1234 posting has already happened in the stock,
if we compare it with this, then
whatever we have invested in ICICI Lombard for long term investors, I
think stay tuned, there is nothing to worry about
and yes, those who
want to invest in it for long term, it was my
mistake that the results here the company has given
these vitamins, if such good
results are coming from the company here, in my opinion,
very good companies are
seen protesting and thirdly, short term
investors are also a bit surrounded, I
think Arun can
touch its peak by May end, I can
attach my entry to 1628, then they have the
board capacity of the inter, going forward
you can take bread in it by going through the
store, so
you will get the result of ICICI Lombard share for the entire quarter, the
album of the entire result in the beginning  You must have got it,
if you have any query then
you can comment in the comment section, I will
definitely listen to your comment every day, so if
you liked the video then please
like the video and do not forget to
subscribe to the channel to get good updates, ok
thank you, have a nice day ahead